

1800 102 2558 | +91 9818882211







Current Designation: Business Analyst

Total Experience: 7 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Current Company: Aditya Birla Finance Ltd.

Notice Period: 15 Days or less

Highest Degree: MBA/PGDM [Other Management]

Pref. Location: Mumbai, Navi Mumbai

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Business Analyst

Current Location: Mumbai

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Married

Key Skills: bpm,business process management,business analysis,presales,project implementation,project delivery,business process modeling,brd,frd,wireframing,functional testing,technical documentation,vendor management,requirement gathering,gap analysis,fsd,uat

Verified : Le Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 12-Jun-19 Last Modified: 31-May-19

Jump to Section | Work Experience | Education | IT Skills | Work Authorization

# Summary

Ambitious professional with more than 7.4 years of IT experience in:

~ Business Process Analysis ~ Document management system ~ Process Improvement

~ Project Implementation ~ Technical Documentation ~ Scrum master

~ Presales consulting ~ Post Production support ~ Functional Testing

#### **Work Experience**

- Aditya Birla Finance Ltd. as Business Analyst May 2018 to Till Date
- ? End to End Implementation of 11 Projects across Newgen BPM/DMS, Enterprise scanning and client facing portals
- ? Performing PMO activities viz. Project tracking, Monthly status review with stakeholders and reports to Senior management
- ? Providing Post Production support for Expense related applications viz. Vendor spend and Employee spend
- ? Working as Scrum Master; fulfilling various ceremonies of Scrum
- ? Involved in the project throughout the SDLC including Project planning, effort estimation, vendor management
- Talisma Corporation as Implementation Consultant Jun 2017 to Apr 2018
- \* Rolled out Centralised Online Admission process for DVET across Maharashtra covering 800+ ITI
- \* Conducted extensive Requirement gathering sessions with DVET employees for E-Governance modules
- \* Designed Custom BPM solutions with detailed AS-IS and TO-BE Process flows in MS Visio
- \* Prepared Dependency structure matrix, Requirement Traceability matrix (RTM) and Wireframes
- \* Prepared Techno-functional documents viz SRS, FSD covering Administrative processes of DVET
- Coached junior BAs' in Requirement analysis and Solution design in line with RFP
- \* Articulated and Negotiated hard with client to ensure Scope control and Project Schedule

#### Edelweiss Agri value Chain Ltd on payroll of MITS as Business Analyst Sep 2015 to Jun 2017

- \* Implemented Warehousing and Financial Accounting applications & their API Integration with peripheral apps
- \* Involved in CR management, Vendor management, Patch deployment and Post Production support
- \* Formulated Business Continuity Plan (BCP) and executed mock drill covering 8 critical applications to ensure seamless business even during server or network failure
- \* Implemented Geo-Tracker Mobile app for tracking employee movement in 800+ warehouses across India
- \* Formulated Access management, CR management and Termination Audit policies for the company

## **Important**

 Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld

### Newgen Software Technologies as Business Analyst

May 2013 to Aug 2015

- \* Implemented Enterprise scanning, BPM and Document management for Credit card, CASA and Loans for Axis bank and ICICI bank
- \* Worked on seamless Integration of multiple 3rd party Web services like CIBIL, Hunter, CTL etc
- \* Prepared Techno-functional documents such as BRD, Scope of Work (SOW), System Requirement Specification (SRS) and FSD
- Developed MS, Test cases and performed System and Functional testing
- \* Single Point of Contact for Training and Post Production issues

## Financial Technologies India Ltd. as Business Analyst

Apr 2011 to Apr 2013

- \* Implemented Retail, Institutional and Agorithmic Trading applications
- \* Presales activities like Product demonstrations, Response to RFP/RFI/RFQ enhancing solution offerings
- \* Prepared Techno-Functional documents and Test cases
- Prepared Product performance, Marketing collaterals and Competitor Analysis reports
- \* Rolled out Product E-mailer campaign for clients

^ Back to Top

#### **Education**

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computers) from AC Patil College of Engineering in 2009

PG: MBA/PGDM (Other Management) from Other in 2011

Other Qualifications/Certifications/Programs: Scrum Master

^ Back to Top

#### **IT Skills**

| S | kill Name        | Version | Last Used | Experience |
|---|------------------|---------|-----------|------------|
| N | /icrosoft Office |         |           |            |
| N | //S Visio        |         |           |            |
| J | IIRA             |         |           |            |
| N | /S-SQL           |         |           |            |

^ Back to Top

## Languages Known

| Language | Proficiency | Read | Write | Speak |
|----------|-------------|------|-------|-------|
| English  | Expert      | ✓    | ✓     | ✓     |
| Hindi    | Expert      | ✓    | ✓     | ✓     |
| Marathi  | Proficient  | ✓    | ✓     | ✓     |
| Urdu     | Expert      |      |       | ✓     |

^ Back to Top

## **Affirmative Action**

## **Work Authorization**

Physically Challenged: No

Countries: India

Job Type: Permanent / Temporary Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQs - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICICIcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.